Grandpa!
Pa!
Dad.
Pa?
Wat.
Is Aim with you?
We need a flashlight.
I'm looking.
Try up here.
What on earth are you doing?
Dad and Aim are gone.
This doesn't work.
- I think there's another one.
- Keep it down.
Try not to make too much
of a fuss or everyone will show up.
The neighbors, they all hate your dad.
They'll call the cops
or they'll wanna perform another exorcism.
Exorcism?
Mom, Dad isn't possessed. He's just sick.
How often is he like this?
Why have you kept this secret?
People around here are mad.
Yeah, well, he's been acting strange
for a while now.
But never this bad before.
You two haven't been around to help.
Aim!
Wan.
They can't have gone out the front.
The gate's locked.
Yeah.
Aim!
Mom, you wait here in case Dad comes back.
And keep your phone on you, okay, Mom?
Wan!
Sadhu. May the spirits
of the forest and the mountains
protect them both.
Do not let them be harmed or killed.
Let them return home safely.
DELUSION
Pa!
Aim!
Wan.
Aim.
Sis.
Look at this.
Wan.
Sis.
Aim!
Wan.
Sis.
Check his phone?
Where is it?
- Aim.
- Grandpa?
Grandpa, it hurts. Let go, Grandpa.
You're hurting me.
What the hell are you doing here?
Why did you come here?
How many times have I told you
not to come here anymore?
- Let go!
- There are ghosts here.
And they'll make you one, too!
Grandpa, let go.
Let go, Grandpa!
- Huh?
- Let go.
Please, Grandpa. It hurts.
Grandpa! Let go!
You're okay.
Don't cry.
To Big Bird.
Congratulations, sir.
- Good on you, buddy.
- Mmm.
You made superintendent.
What's your secret?
Come on, tell us.
No secret, brother.
I just did my job. That's all.
But I promise I won't forget you guys.
Better not, you motherfucker.
- I'm behind you, Big Bird.
- Yeah.
Hey.
What's the big hurry?
No time to waste,
unlike you guys.
You're full of shit.
Your precinct's dead.
We both know
it's like a graveyard in there.
Relax the ego, my friend.
Just do whatever the boss tells you to.
You gotta suck up a little bit.
That's how you'll get back to Bangkok.
Playing the hero
won't get you anywhere.
Learn from a master.
I think you're a bit drunk.
Go back and sit down, eh?
Even if you were such a hero,
or some kind of genius,
if your boss doesn't want you…
you ain't got nothing.
You get it?
Here we go!
- Sir Bird.
- Big Bird.
Cheers!
Everybody freeze! Hands up, all of you!
- Don't move.
- Hands up!
Put that down.
- Gather all the evidence.
- Yes, sir.
On the ground.
You're under arrest for operating
an illegal online gambling site,
money laundering, and computer fraud.
Take them away.
- Move!
- Yes, sir.
Come on. Hands up you heads!
On your knees.
So why did you make such a scene?
Your instructions were to keep them
under surveillance and then inform me.
I seized the opportunity to catch them
red handed with the evidence.
And now it's a media circus.
An unauthorized operation.
If you have a problem
with the way I do things around here,
you could be better working
somewhere else.
I apologize
for my officer's behavior, sir.
We're gonna need about ten million
to put this to bed…
Hello?
How long will you be?
Okay. Thanks. See you soon.
I think we're close.
You hear that?
Aim!
Aim, can you hear me?
Aim.
Sis, wait. What are you doing?
Where are you going? Sis.
Calm down, sis.
I'm here. Don't worry.
Take a deep breath.
That's it. Breathe slowly.
Wan.
I think if we go in there now
where there's no trail to follow,
we could get hopelessly lost.
And then we will never find them.
Wat, we can't see if he's looking.
We should head back to base and wait.
Wait for help to arrive.
If you end up missing too,
things will just be worse.
Let's go back and wait.
Come on, sis. Let's go.
Hello, ma'am.
Where's your daughter?
What's the old man up to?
He'll be back in a little while.
He went out for a walk.
The kids, they're out looking.
He took your grandchild with him.
When did they go missing?
I don't know what time it was.
Anyway, you're the police.
So why are you standing
around here asking questions?
You're not from around here.
How could you help anyway?
Officer, I found Aim's tablet
in the forest.
It's coming on now.
Does dementia normally cause
noses to bleed like that, doctor?
Uh, no.
So that means it's not normal.
Even if he's not acting so rational,
my dad would hurt his own grandson.
Why did you call the police?
It's just add to people
calling him possessed.
As if we don't have
enough to do right now.
That's all you care about?
What about your grandson?
Of course I care.
This is a family matter.
We should handle it.
What are we going to do now?
If the police arrest him and lock him up,
what will we do then?
Can you tell me what Aim was wearing?
A T-shirt, light green,
and plaid pajama pants.
Okay.
I'm gonna head out now.
You just wait out here.
A patrol unit will be here soon.
This is Sasidit.
The child is 150 centimeters tall.
He's wearing a light green T-shirt
and plaid pajama pants.
Sergent, when you arrive,
check around the house first,
and split up into teams.
Copy that.
- Let's go.
- Yeah.
I grew up here. I won't be a burden.
Wat, don't go with them.
Stay with me here. I'm scared.
Be careful, sis.
Hey.
Let's go home, Grandpa.
Listen, why are you crying for? Eh?
Here, you take this.
You said you wanted to go fishing
at the waterfall.
That's where I'm taking you.
So don't cry.
You're the one who wanted it.
Nothing to report here as of yet.
Waterfall.
I'll go there and check it out
Sergeant, I missed that. Say it again.
He said something about the waterfall.
It's not too far from here.
Okay, Sergeant. Check it out.
- Keep me updated, okay?
- Yes, sir.
Aim.
I think your dad is deteriorating.
How would you know?
He…
These episodes, they're…
happening more often now.
He may present a danger to others.
So what should I do?
I don't know, I guess
you just have to work it out, that's all.
It's a family matters,
but if this keeps happening,
then things will only get worse.
And now he's lost in a forest
with a child.
What on earth is he thinking?
Once he gets his medication,
he'll be fine.
My dad's not violent.
He won't hurt anyone.
Aim!
Here, Mom. Let me help.
I'm okay.
Your sister, she's never much helps to me.
Who knows what she does over
at her rich husband's house?
They're probably thinking
her parents didn't raise her properly.
Here, eat up.
Mom, aren't you scared about Dad?
If he died or just vanished,
that's still better than possessed.
Nee.
Hello, Uncle.
It's been a while, hasn't it?
Have you been well?
Mom, your brother's here.
Phii Pong, he hasn't
brought the boy back yet?
Here.
Write Aim's name here on the chest.
And if Narong comes back,
I'll perform a quick ritual.
It will help him a lot.
Uh, uncle, you need to stop
all these nonsense.
My father is just ill.
And what's this?
Please just take it away.
No, you keep it.
The ghost will not leave easily.
It must be exorcised or it will never go.
A boy from the city like you
doesn't know these things.
Your mother, she grew up with this forest.
She knows what needs to be done.
Uh, okay then, Uncle. You know what?
Let's just go our own ways.
I'll see to it that Dad
gets medical treatment
and you go ahead
and do whatever rituals you like.
But I want you
to leave my parents out of it.
Promise me that.
The modern medicines,
they can't cure things like these.
A shaman like me, I've saved
more lives than you could count.
Let me know what you decide, sister.
Aim!
- Aim!
Aim.
Aim!
Hey. Step back. Step back.
This is a crime scene.
You must listen.
Just wait here and let me see.
Sergeant, you copy?
I found a body.
It looks like Mued, the first missing boy.
I'm not far from the waterfall.
Look for a large tree
wrapped in three-colored ribbons.
Notify the station
and get the medical examiner down here.
Over.
Aim's…
Come in, Sergeant.
I believe Aim is not far from my location.
Grandpa.
Hurry up.
Grandpa, we should go home.
Mom will be worried.
Look, can you see the fish?
You wanna see?
Go on. Look.
Over there, see, so many fish. Look.
Can you see? Look, there.
See, there are fish.
Right here, and over there.
Fish.
The fish, there, right here. Lots of them.
So many fish.
Right here, look.
Where are you going?
Don't you want to see the fish?
Grandpa, I'm scared.
I am not your grandpa.
Kids like you are no good.
You need to learn. I'm going to teach you.
Phii Pong.
You really are Phii Pong.
Help, Mom!
Help!
Mom!
Naughty kids like you…
belong here in the forest.
You're not going home to your mom.
Go on. Get in the water.
Now!
No, don't, Grandpa. Don't!
I don't want to. Grandpa, let go.
Grandpa, don't!
Grandpa!
Let go, Grandpa.
Grandpa, I want to go home.
Let me go!
Get into the water.
- No, Grandpa! No!
- Go!
Let me go!
Aim! Aim!
Aim!
Calm down.
I've got you.
You're safe now.
Aim.
Aim, son.
Over there.
Take him away.
Come on.
Aim.
Come on now.
Let's go.
Have you got a bandage?
Inspector.
Could you please tell the other officers
to be gentle with my father?
He's quite confused.
Aim.
You see what you've done?
All you do is bringing trouble
to our house.
We did everything Sak told us to.
But my grandson still isn't here.
Please calm down, and don't cry.
Wait for the shaman to speak.
It's all right.
Let her cry.
Her grandson is already dead.
See, the ghost has taken him.
It is an evil force.
There's nothing more to do.
Collect the soil and the teeth,
have them all tested.
The killer must've left something behind.
But what kind of evidence
would a ghost leave?
You must be careful, Inspector.
The ghost could possess any of us.
If the killer really is a ghost,
then we shall arrest that ghost.
You shouldn't joke, Inspector.
You know, locals believe
in this Phii Pong.
And decades ago, right here
at the same spot, a child was killed.
Lying face down.
Like this.
Teeth and guts ripped out, just the same.
Sergeant.
I think the people here…
have seen too many horror movies.
How does a spirit pick up a knife?
And then rips someone's guts out, eh?
Please forgive me.
It's about your grandson, ma'am.
I'm sorry to tell you,
police have located
his body in the forest.
Right now, the body is…
Tell us what to do.
Please guide us, shaman.
We must first find out
who it inhabits.
Anyone…
who has been lurking
around the forest during these nights,
someone acting strangely
with darkness to their face
from this twisted being, we must exorcise
the ghost within.
We found hairs on the body.
The DNA test maybe able
to identify our suspect.
You don't remember anything?
You understand what I'm saying?
A little help.
Hey.
How's Aim doing?
He's under observation.
But I think he'll be okay.
That's such a relief to hear.
Mmm.
How's Dad getting along?
Sis, I have to go.
How is he, Officer?
Can you tell us how my is father?
He hasn't responded to anything.
But, Shaman, won't this
make things worse for Aunt Nee?
I warned her.
I told her to exorcise Phii Pong.
And now someone's dead.
My grandson is fine now.
And his mother won't to press any charges.
Can you let him go?
This is a murder case.
He's now a suspect.
I'm sorry, ma'am,
we're unable to release him.
Subtitle translation by: Parida Kim